localbillinglimited.com 2010-02-23

# LocalBilling - LocalBilling Privacy Policy

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
| Home >>> Local Billing Privacy Policy  
---  
  
Summary

Your private financial information is secure. Local Billing will never divulge your personal, private financial information to anyone for any reason. |   
---|---  
  
What This Privacy Policy Covers

• This policy covers how Local Billing treats personal information that Local Billing collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Local Billing products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

• This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Local Billing does not own or control, or to people that Local Billing does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Local Billing associated companies such as Visa, MasterCard and Telecom providers which have their own privacy policies.

Information Collection and Use

General

• Local Billing collects personal information when you register withLocal Billing, when you use Local Billing products or services,  
when you visit Local Billing pages or the pages of certain Local Billing partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Local Billing may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

• When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry and we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with Local Billing and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

• Local Billing collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

• Local Billing automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Local  
Billing cookie information, and the page you request.

• Local Billing uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

• Local Billing does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies. Local Billing Privacy Policy Your privacy is our first priority. about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies.

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and  
Preferences

General

• You can edit your [Local Billing Account Information](https://secure.localbillinglimited.com/user_admin.php) at any time. 

• New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit  
this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

• We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Local Billing service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Local Billing Newsletter, that are considered part of your Local Billing account

• You can delete your Local Billing account by visiting our [User Administration](https://secure.localbillinglimited.com/user_admin.php) page.

Confidentiality and Security

• We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

• We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information  
about you.

• To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security  
at Local Billing.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

• Local Billing may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Local Billing account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us

|  January 12th, 2009

**Las Vegas**  
Meet the team in Las Vegas, Nevada.   
  
---  
November 19th, 2008

**Los Angeles**  
Meet Clay Douglass, CEO, and Mitch Platt, President, to find out more on the complete service Local Billing offers and more importantly how they can it help your company grow it's e-commerce revenue.   
  
October 17th, 2008

**Panama**  
Meet Mitch Platt, President and Andrew Hellner, Director of the Entertainment Segment in October in a more personal setting to find out what's new at Local Billing.   
  
September 25th, 2008

**Amsterdam**  
Meet the team in Europe to find our exactly how Local Billing can help grow your international revenue. Lukas Taylor, new account manager will be on hand for the first time to answer any questions.   
  
August 8th, 2008

**Miami**  
Be the first to personally meet the new Local Billing directive team and find out how their world-class knowledge and expertise will ensure Local Billing will deliver on your performance. They will also be on hand to answer any questions. 

Read more news...
